<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The Yankee</title>
    <link>https://the-yankee.github.io/news/</link>
    <description>Recent content on The Yankee</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://the-yankee.github.io/news/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Alternate History Series - Hamilton &amp; Burr - What If Alexander Hamilton Had Lived?</title>
      <link>https://the-yankee.github.io/news/post/2019/07/23/alternate-history-series-hamilton-burr-what-if-alexander-hamilton-had-lived/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://the-yankee.github.io/news/post/2019/07/23/alternate-history-series-hamilton-burr-what-if-alexander-hamilton-had-lived/</guid>
      <description>Alexander Hamilton, the first Secretary of Treasury, a hero &amp;amp; scholar, war-hero, and Founding Father of the United States of America, was one of the most important and influential men in American history while being one of the youngest.  Alexander died on July 24, 1804, aged 47 years old, pouring gushing blood on the soil of the country he fought for and built out of dust. Standing ten feet away from his cold, blue corpse stood his one time best friend, Vice President Aaron Burr, holding a piped smoking continental dueling pistol.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>America Today - The End of Moderation - Echo Chambers of Extremism</title>
      <link>https://the-yankee.github.io/news/post/2019/07/23/america-today-the-end-of-moderation-echo-chambers-of-extremism/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://the-yankee.github.io/news/post/2019/07/23/america-today-the-end-of-moderation-echo-chambers-of-extremism/</guid>
      <description>In America today, it seems as if tensions are growing exponentially. It seems as if our society has an animosity that continues to multiply more and more until someday, the hatred will engulf our society as a whole as it did 150 years ago. Is this a warning? Is it a sign that we have not learned since our horrible cost of millions of lives lost in the American Civil War?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>China &amp; Tariffs - Is it Constitutional - Is it Needed?</title>
      <link>https://the-yankee.github.io/news/post/2019/07/23/china-tariffs-is-it-constitutional-is-it-needed/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://the-yankee.github.io/news/post/2019/07/23/china-tariffs-is-it-constitutional-is-it-needed/</guid>
      <description>Much hysteria has appeared over the past few days, in response to President Donald Trump’s recent comments on being somewhat supportive of tariffs on Chinese trade.
So what’s all this? Trump? Tariffs? These have pretty much become swear words depending on who you’re talking to. First, let’s break this down in a non-controversial way.
Ok, so- what’s a tariff? A tariff, according to Meriam Webster (link down below), is: (noun) A schedule of duties imposed by a government on imported or in some countries exported goods.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Free Speech - Why America NEEDS Hate Speech - First Amendment Legislation</title>
      <link>https://the-yankee.github.io/news/post/2019/07/23/free-speech-why-america-needs-hate-speech-first-amendment-legislation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://the-yankee.github.io/news/post/2019/07/23/free-speech-why-america-needs-hate-speech-first-amendment-legislation/</guid>
      <description>Within recent events, whether it be the bomb threats on Democratic Candidates, the Congressmen massacre, or the “Trump Whistle Blowing” events, society has blamed public speakers and their perceived message of “whistling for” or “inciting” violence for these horrific events of inhumanity.
Both Republicans and Democrats have been quick to blame the opposite side for “inciting” violence or “whistling” for it. In 2017, former presidential candidate, Bernie Sanders, at a rally for public assembly, he exclaimed how a healthcare bill which was just passed by Congress was going to “kill millions of people!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Immigration Migration - The U.S. Immigration Problem Solution - Federalist 46.</title>
      <link>https://the-yankee.github.io/news/post/2019/07/23/immigration-migration-the-u.s.-immigration-problem-solution-federalist-46./</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://the-yankee.github.io/news/post/2019/07/23/immigration-migration-the-u.s.-immigration-problem-solution-federalist-46./</guid>
      <description>The immigration problem in the United States has been publicized as one of the most divisive issues that divides the modern political biosphere. Both Republicans and Democrats have chosen their sides of this issue; conservatives, taking mostly isolationist and defensive standpoints on illegal immigration, and liberals, taking a more sympathetic standpoint on immigrants.
Southern Republican states are the main campaigners for border security and reform, while Western Democratic states endorse sanctuary states for pardoning illegal immigrants.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Minutemen - Minute News - An Update on Bills on Congress Floor</title>
      <link>https://the-yankee.github.io/news/post/2019/07/23/minutemen-minute-news-an-update-on-bills-on-congress-floor/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://the-yankee.github.io/news/post/2019/07/23/minutemen-minute-news-an-update-on-bills-on-congress-floor/</guid>
      <description>This week, Congress had several new bills which are yet to be discussed. Some will likely be passed when reviewed, some are unworthy of even being on the floor. This week, The Yankee news team is determined to keep you informed with all current bills. Our Minutemen, The Yankee’s very own Chief Financial Officer, Pranik Chainani, and Freelance reporter, teenager, Carson Wolf get inside information on the news within congress. We give you Minute News with the Minutemen!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>President Wars - Episode I - Trump vs Jefferson - The Trump Train Strikes Back - Who’s the Better President?</title>
      <link>https://the-yankee.github.io/news/post/2019/07/23/president-wars-episode-i-trump-vs-jefferson-the-trump-train-strikes-back-whos-the-better-president/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://the-yankee.github.io/news/post/2019/07/23/president-wars-episode-i-trump-vs-jefferson-the-trump-train-strikes-back-whos-the-better-president/</guid>
      <description>Two of the most influential men of Conservative influence and beliefs who were determined enough to win the office of President of the United States, Thomas Jefferson &amp;amp; Donald Trump were and are both responsible for an era of change in the political biosphere of the country. Despite their influence and change, good or bad, they have become prominent figures of the conservative and modern Republican movement. But which of these huge figures was a better president?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The American Debt Problem - The Approaching Catastrophe - How Do We Stop It?</title>
      <link>https://the-yankee.github.io/news/post/2019/04/02/the-american-debt-problem-the-approaching-catastrophe-how-do-we-stop-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://the-yankee.github.io/news/post/2019/04/02/the-american-debt-problem-the-approaching-catastrophe-how-do-we-stop-it/</guid>
      <description>The United States, a nation built and based upon a system of financial and economic stability, has inherited a colossal debt of $22 trillion USD. Much of this debt has been inherited in the past century.
Since the debt rose to $1 trillion in 1981, the debt since has taken on an extra $21 trillion in under 40 years.
The United States’ debt continues to grow today. The debt is projected to grow exponentially, another 230%, by 2050.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Founding Fathers - The Revolutionary Rejects - What Made Them So Incredible?</title>
      <link>https://the-yankee.github.io/news/post/2019/04/01/the-founding-fathers-the-revolutionary-rejects-what-made-them-so-incredible/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://the-yankee.github.io/news/post/2019/04/01/the-founding-fathers-the-revolutionary-rejects-what-made-them-so-incredible/</guid>
      <description>A hot summer’s day, in early July, a group of criminals began the process that would be remembered from then until the day of the last man. These criminals, united by nothing but their valor and determination to create a strong foundation, began the process, known as the American Revolution.
These criminals were not traditional criminals, more renaissance criminals: men who were not led astray by the common, traditional beliefs which fellow men tended to cling to, only adopting practices which would change their lives for the better.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>History Buffs - Hamilton Series - The Forgotten Founder - The Man Who Killed Alexander Hamilton</title>
      <link>https://the-yankee.github.io/news/post/2019/03/27/history-buffs-hamilton-series-the-forgotten-founder-the-man-who-killed-alexander-hamilton/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://the-yankee.github.io/news/post/2019/03/27/history-buffs-hamilton-series-the-forgotten-founder-the-man-who-killed-alexander-hamilton/</guid>
      <description>In the popular hip-hop, popping extravaganza, Hamilton tells the story of the ten dollars founding father, Alexander Hamilton. From beginning to end, it recognizes the loudness of his actions but the quietness of his legacy and recognition. However, this is not the case today. Hamilton is not only one of the greatest known heroes of our country’s founding, but he’s known as a symbol of truth, justice, and reformation around the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>History Buffs - Red Dead Redemption II Special - How Accurate Is It?</title>
      <link>https://the-yankee.github.io/news/post/2019/03/15/history-buffs-red-dead-redemption-ii-special-how-accurate-is-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://the-yankee.github.io/news/post/2019/03/15/history-buffs-red-dead-redemption-ii-special-how-accurate-is-it/</guid>
      <description>In 1899, the West’s wild antics had been put to rest. Arthur Morgan, a southern outlaw, is left in the now shrinking wild west, forcing him to move south to avoid the law. His gang, led by a good friend, Dutch Van Der Linde, move down south in search of money and new opportunities. Morgan uses his quick-witted thinking along with his trigger finger &amp;amp; fists to lead their gang to a new beginning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>History Buffs Series - Hamilton Series - What Really Happened to Burr?</title>
      <link>https://the-yankee.github.io/news/post/2019/03/14/history-buffs-series-hamilton-series-what-really-happened-to-burr/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://the-yankee.github.io/news/post/2019/03/14/history-buffs-series-hamilton-series-what-really-happened-to-burr/</guid>
      <description>Preamble: In the Broadway Hip-Hop Musical, Hamilton, written by the incredibly talented star, Lin Manuel Miranda, Aaron Burr, the cold-blooded murderer of Alexander Hamilton, tells the story ofd the man he killed: founding father, Alexander Hamilton. Hamilton comes from Saint Croix to New York City, in search of refining his legacy and rising up to a new standard of living. The ambitious Alexander makes quick work, as he takes shots of ambition with his new group of friends: including John Laurens, Marquis de Lafayette, Hercules Mulligan, and his future killer, Aaron Burr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Federalist Papers Series - Federalist No. 46 - The American Gun Problem</title>
      <link>https://the-yankee.github.io/news/post/2019/03/12/federalist-papers-series-federalist-no.-46-the-american-gun-problem/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://the-yankee.github.io/news/post/2019/03/12/federalist-papers-series-federalist-no.-46-the-american-gun-problem/</guid>
      <description>Preamble: The Federalist Papers are a series of essays, describing the rationale and legitimacy for a new American Constitution. The writers, Alexander Hamilton, James Madison, and John Jay strived to bring upon a new era of liberty and truth in their newly founded nation. During this time, the state of their nation was nothing less of disunified nation states, living separately of each other. The new constitution was a way of uniting the states, founding the United States of America.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>President’s Day - The Unlikely Best President Ever!</title>
      <link>https://the-yankee.github.io/news/post/2019/03/05/presidents-day-the-unlikely-best-president-ever/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://the-yankee.github.io/news/post/2019/03/05/presidents-day-the-unlikely-best-president-ever/</guid>
      <description>With the recent passing of President’s Day, the office of the presidency is reminisced upon. The office has been held 45 different times by 44 different men. These men have served our country and changed it in several different ways, big and small, which is why we honor them, this presidents day.
Presidents like Abraham Lincoln, George Washington, and John F. Kennedy are often regarded as the U.S. However, it’s very unlikely that when discussing the greatest presidents in America you bring up Grover Cleaveland.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Congress - Passes Bill to Require Extended Gun Background Checks</title>
      <link>https://the-yankee.github.io/news/post/2019/02/28/congress-passes-bill-to-require-extended-gun-background-checks/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://the-yankee.github.io/news/post/2019/02/28/congress-passes-bill-to-require-extended-gun-background-checks/</guid>
      <description>On February 28th, Congress passed a bill, requiring all gun manufacturers to take extended background checks with all gun sales. Rep. Mike Thomas, in district CA, and Pete King, New York Representative, proposed the bill, seeking reform with illegal and unlicensed firearms.
This act clamps down on drug dealers, restricting all from transferring illegal or unlicensed firearms to third parties until a background check has been completed.
Nowadays, current laws allow the sale to still commence, given that the provided dealer’s discretion is approved, even if the background check is not completed in a 3 days time span.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trump - The House Rejects Emergency Order - Will the Wall Happen?</title>
      <link>https://the-yankee.github.io/news/post/2019/02/28/trump-the-house-rejects-emergency-order-will-the-wall-happen/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://the-yankee.github.io/news/post/2019/02/28/trump-the-house-rejects-emergency-order-will-the-wall-happen/</guid>
      <description>On February 26, President Donald Trump’s emergency executive order to bypass Congress and change the course of funding to a border wall was blocked, in a vote of 245 to 182.
Earlier this year, President Trump has rejected the proper funding for a border wall, calling for a government shutdown. Ever since, Trump’s goal has been to ensure a future of a southern border with a physical barrier. Later, President Trump declared a national emergency, had the conflict not been resolved by February 15th, allowing production of a border wall without support in the legislative body.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Info Wars Lawsuit - Fake News - Is Freedom of Speech &amp; Press Still Necessary?</title>
      <link>https://the-yankee.github.io/news/post/2019/02/26/info-wars-lawsuit-fake-news-is-freedom-of-speech-press-still-necessary/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://the-yankee.github.io/news/post/2019/02/26/info-wars-lawsuit-fake-news-is-freedom-of-speech-press-still-necessary/</guid>
      <description>Alex Jones, spokesman, and founder of the streaming network, Info Wars, has been filed suit against by families of the Sandy Hook Massacre survivors.
In February, it was released that families had filed suit against Jones in a defamation trial, accusing him of misinformation on behalf of the deaths of their children.
Jones claimed, on his podcast, that the victims and shooter in the massacre were indeed actors.
The families declared this statement “a conspiracy theory”, disapproving of the statement and the story, as a whole.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trump - America Will Never Be Socialist Country -- Will it?</title>
      <link>https://the-yankee.github.io/news/post/2019/02/25/trump-america-will-never-be-socialist-country-will-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://the-yankee.github.io/news/post/2019/02/25/trump-america-will-never-be-socialist-country-will-it/</guid>
      <description>President Donald Trump, ever since he has taken office, has taken an anti-socialist stance, while promoting capitalist ideals.
Will and should America ever be a socialist country?
The discussion, regarding socialism vs capitalism, has gained many spectators, as they are seen as the only two futures of the economic &amp;amp; political structure of our country. Should socialism, a system which benefits the society as a whole replace capitalism, a system which benefits the individuals within society?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Muslim Heroes in Iraq - No One Left Behind</title>
      <link>https://the-yankee.github.io/news/post/2019/02/17/the-muslim-heroes-in-iraq-no-one-left-behind/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://the-yankee.github.io/news/post/2019/02/17/the-muslim-heroes-in-iraq-no-one-left-behind/</guid>
      <description>Link: http://nooneleft.org/
In 2014, during the Iraqi warring conflicts, over 20,000 people died in one year. More than 6,000 of them were civilians. Ever since the U.S. entered the conflict, the death toll has thus reached over 500,000 casualties.
During this conflict, the U.S. received much help from local Iraqi civilians. Many civilians offered their assistance as translators and cooperators for the United States Military. These interpreters knew the area which Marines were dealing with, offering an important knowledge to the Marines.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trump - Government Shutdown Affects Future American Plans</title>
      <link>https://the-yankee.github.io/news/post/2019/02/11/trump-government-shutdown-affects-future-american-plans/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://the-yankee.github.io/news/post/2019/02/11/trump-government-shutdown-affects-future-american-plans/</guid>
      <description>President Donald Trump has shown the United States his determination in getting his way in American politics. The government shutdown from late December 2018 to present has affected the United States beyond extent.
The federal shutdown, an executive order, drafted by President Trump, in response to the democratic majority of the Senate disapproving of “The Wall.
So, this shutdown; is it justified? Is Trump right? Or is Trump the devil in disguise, as he ruins our sweet nation?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trump - How Does He Rank Up Against Other Presidents?</title>
      <link>https://the-yankee.github.io/news/post/2019/02/06/trump-how-does-he-rank-up-against-other-presidents/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://the-yankee.github.io/news/post/2019/02/06/trump-how-does-he-rank-up-against-other-presidents/</guid>
      <description>President Trump is a divisive president, to say the least. It’s a common belief, nowadays, that you either hate him or you love him.
Many have accused President Trump of illegal and unpresidential action, even invoking legal action. Is it justified? We don’t know yet, but it does influence us when discussing how President Donald Trump is viewed when comparing him to former U.S Presidents.
The office of U.S presidency has been held 45 times by 44 different people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trump -- How Constitutional Are His Policies?</title>
      <link>https://the-yankee.github.io/news/post/2019/01/30/trump-how-constitutional-are-his-policies/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://the-yankee.github.io/news/post/2019/01/30/trump-how-constitutional-are-his-policies/</guid>
      <description>President Donald J. Trump is a divisive president, to say the least. He is often described as ‘unfit’ to be President of the United States. Whether this statement is true or not, are his policies constitutional?
His policies have inspired controversy upon both sides of the political spectrum, but should his executive orders hold up in the supreme court?
First, let’s look at the behemoth of the Trump Administration: ‘The Wall’.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ranking the Top Five Presidents of the United States</title>
      <link>https://the-yankee.github.io/news/post/2019/01/09/ranking-the-top-five-presidents-of-the-united-states/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://the-yankee.github.io/news/post/2019/01/09/ranking-the-top-five-presidents-of-the-united-states/</guid>
      <description>Since 1789, the United States of America has had 45 separate Presidents. However, only 44 different people have taken office, as Grover Cleveland served two non-consecutive terms. Presidents, old and young, have impacted this great country and made it what it is today. Their effort and sacrifice which they’ve given to us all are much appreciated. Although all of these fine men have given much, some stand out as giving a lot for this country.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trump - Border Wall Would’ve Stopped California Illegal Alien From Murdering Police Officer.</title>
      <link>https://the-yankee.github.io/news/post/2019/01/09/trump-border-wall-wouldve-stopped-california-illegal-alien-from-murdering-police-officer./</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://the-yankee.github.io/news/post/2019/01/09/trump-border-wall-wouldve-stopped-california-illegal-alien-from-murdering-police-officer./</guid>
      <description>President Donald J. Trump, the 45th President of the United States has vocally preached of a border wall to stop the illegal trafficking through the Mexican-American border. Trump has received a lot of backlash for this belief. However, recent events in California have drawn many to Trump’s side.
Early Wednesday morning, an illegal Mexican immigrant (NAME WITHHELD) murdered a Newman County Corporal, Ronil Singh after he was pulled over for drunk driving.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trump - Do the Tax Cuts Hold Up Today?</title>
      <link>https://the-yankee.github.io/news/post/2019/01/09/trump-do-the-tax-cuts-hold-up-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://the-yankee.github.io/news/post/2019/01/09/trump-do-the-tax-cuts-hold-up-today/</guid>
      <description>45th President, Donald Trump has preached of his achievements relating to his tax cuts and bringing jobs to the United States.
Yes, it is true that his tax cuts have impacted many Americans and the American job market.
Trump’s Tax Cut &amp;amp; Jobs Act has decreased individual tax returns by about 4 to 7 percent. With this new tax plan enacted, the local and state governments are impacted. As mortgage &amp;amp; interest rates that are funded by the federal government and held up by the locals, they are now required to follow the new, broad tax base set of rules.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About The Yankee and Statement</title>
      <link>https://the-yankee.github.io/news/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://the-yankee.github.io/news/about/</guid>
      <description>Statement: The Yankee
Preamble: We the people, in order to improve the knowledge and informing of the general public establish The Yankee, a series of essays and articles of historical and political context. The pieces published by The Yankee are strictly opinionated and are not to be used against in a court of law. Information not approved by any sources are strictly anecdotal sources or abstract/concrete ideas with no guaranteed factual evidence.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>