<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Presidents on The Yankee</title>
    <link>https://the-yankee.github.io/news/categories/presidents/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Presidents on The Yankee</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://the-yankee.github.io/news/categories/presidents/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>President’s Day - The Unlikely Best President Ever!</title>
      <link>https://the-yankee.github.io/news/post/2019/03/05/presidents-day-the-unlikely-best-president-ever/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://the-yankee.github.io/news/post/2019/03/05/presidents-day-the-unlikely-best-president-ever/</guid>
      <description>With the recent passing of President’s Day, the office of the presidency is reminisced upon. The office has been held 45 different times by 44 different men. These men have served our country and changed it in several different ways, big and small, which is why we honor them, this presidents day.
Presidents like Abraham Lincoln, George Washington, and John F. Kennedy are often regarded as the U.S. However, it’s very unlikely that when discussing the greatest presidents in America you bring up Grover Cleaveland.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trump - America Will Never Be Socialist Country -- Will it?</title>
      <link>https://the-yankee.github.io/news/post/2019/02/25/trump-america-will-never-be-socialist-country-will-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://the-yankee.github.io/news/post/2019/02/25/trump-america-will-never-be-socialist-country-will-it/</guid>
      <description>President Donald Trump, ever since he has taken office, has taken an anti-socialist stance, while promoting capitalist ideals.
Will and should America ever be a socialist country?
The discussion, regarding socialism vs capitalism, has gained many spectators, as they are seen as the only two futures of the economic &amp;amp; political structure of our country. Should socialism, a system which benefits the society as a whole replace capitalism, a system which benefits the individuals within society?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trump - How Does He Rank Up Against Other Presidents?</title>
      <link>https://the-yankee.github.io/news/post/2019/02/06/trump-how-does-he-rank-up-against-other-presidents/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://the-yankee.github.io/news/post/2019/02/06/trump-how-does-he-rank-up-against-other-presidents/</guid>
      <description>President Trump is a divisive president, to say the least. It’s a common belief, nowadays, that you either hate him or you love him.
Many have accused President Trump of illegal and unpresidential action, even invoking legal action. Is it justified? We don’t know yet, but it does influence us when discussing how President Donald Trump is viewed when comparing him to former U.S Presidents.
The office of U.S presidency has been held 45 times by 44 different people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ranking the Top Five Presidents of the United States</title>
      <link>https://the-yankee.github.io/news/post/2019/01/09/ranking-the-top-five-presidents-of-the-united-states/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://the-yankee.github.io/news/post/2019/01/09/ranking-the-top-five-presidents-of-the-united-states/</guid>
      <description>Since 1789, the United States of America has had 45 separate Presidents. However, only 44 different people have taken office, as Grover Cleveland served two non-consecutive terms. Presidents, old and young, have impacted this great country and made it what it is today. Their effort and sacrifice which they’ve given to us all are much appreciated. Although all of these fine men have given much, some stand out as giving a lot for this country.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>