<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Trump on The Yankee</title>
    <link>https://the-yankee.github.io/news/categories/trump/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Trump on The Yankee</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://the-yankee.github.io/news/categories/trump/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>China &amp; Tariffs - Is it Constitutional - Is it Needed?</title>
      <link>https://the-yankee.github.io/news/post/2019/07/23/china-tariffs-is-it-constitutional-is-it-needed/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://the-yankee.github.io/news/post/2019/07/23/china-tariffs-is-it-constitutional-is-it-needed/</guid>
      <description>Much hysteria has appeared over the past few days, in response to President Donald Trump’s recent comments on being somewhat supportive of tariffs on Chinese trade.
So what’s all this? Trump? Tariffs? These have pretty much become swear words depending on who you’re talking to. First, let’s break this down in a non-controversial way.
Ok, so- what’s a tariff? A tariff, according to Meriam Webster (link down below), is: (noun) A schedule of duties imposed by a government on imported or in some countries exported goods.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trump - Government Shutdown Affects Future American Plans</title>
      <link>https://the-yankee.github.io/news/post/2019/02/11/trump-government-shutdown-affects-future-american-plans/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://the-yankee.github.io/news/post/2019/02/11/trump-government-shutdown-affects-future-american-plans/</guid>
      <description>President Donald Trump has shown the United States his determination in getting his way in American politics. The government shutdown from late December 2018 to present has affected the United States beyond extent.
The federal shutdown, an executive order, drafted by President Trump, in response to the democratic majority of the Senate disapproving of “The Wall.
So, this shutdown; is it justified? Is Trump right? Or is Trump the devil in disguise, as he ruins our sweet nation?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>