<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Trump&#39;s America on The Yankee</title>
    <link>https://the-yankee.github.io/news/categories/trumps-america/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Trump&#39;s America on The Yankee</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://the-yankee.github.io/news/categories/trumps-america/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Trump - The House Rejects Emergency Order - Will the Wall Happen?</title>
      <link>https://the-yankee.github.io/news/post/2019/02/28/trump-the-house-rejects-emergency-order-will-the-wall-happen/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://the-yankee.github.io/news/post/2019/02/28/trump-the-house-rejects-emergency-order-will-the-wall-happen/</guid>
      <description>On February 26, President Donald Trump’s emergency executive order to bypass Congress and change the course of funding to a border wall was blocked, in a vote of 245 to 182.
Earlier this year, President Trump has rejected the proper funding for a border wall, calling for a government shutdown. Ever since, Trump’s goal has been to ensure a future of a southern border with a physical barrier. Later, President Trump declared a national emergency, had the conflict not been resolved by February 15th, allowing production of a border wall without support in the legislative body.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trump - Do the Tax Cuts Hold Up Today?</title>
      <link>https://the-yankee.github.io/news/post/2019/01/09/trump-do-the-tax-cuts-hold-up-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://the-yankee.github.io/news/post/2019/01/09/trump-do-the-tax-cuts-hold-up-today/</guid>
      <description>45th President, Donald Trump has preached of his achievements relating to his tax cuts and bringing jobs to the United States.
Yes, it is true that his tax cuts have impacted many Americans and the American job market.
Trump’s Tax Cut &amp;amp; Jobs Act has decreased individual tax returns by about 4 to 7 percent. With this new tax plan enacted, the local and state governments are impacted. As mortgage &amp;amp; interest rates that are funded by the federal government and held up by the locals, they are now required to follow the new, broad tax base set of rules.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>