<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>History Buffs on The Yankee</title>
    <link>https://the-yankee.github.io/news/categories/history-buffs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in History Buffs on The Yankee</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://the-yankee.github.io/news/categories/history-buffs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>History Buffs - Hamilton Series - The Forgotten Founder - The Man Who Killed Alexander Hamilton</title>
      <link>https://the-yankee.github.io/news/post/2019/03/27/history-buffs-hamilton-series-the-forgotten-founder-the-man-who-killed-alexander-hamilton/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://the-yankee.github.io/news/post/2019/03/27/history-buffs-hamilton-series-the-forgotten-founder-the-man-who-killed-alexander-hamilton/</guid>
      <description>In the popular hip-hop, popping extravaganza, Hamilton tells the story of the ten dollars founding father, Alexander Hamilton. From beginning to end, it recognizes the loudness of his actions but the quietness of his legacy and recognition. However, this is not the case today. Hamilton is not only one of the greatest known heroes of our country’s founding, but he’s known as a symbol of truth, justice, and reformation around the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>History Buffs - Red Dead Redemption II Special - How Accurate Is It?</title>
      <link>https://the-yankee.github.io/news/post/2019/03/15/history-buffs-red-dead-redemption-ii-special-how-accurate-is-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://the-yankee.github.io/news/post/2019/03/15/history-buffs-red-dead-redemption-ii-special-how-accurate-is-it/</guid>
      <description>In 1899, the West’s wild antics had been put to rest. Arthur Morgan, a southern outlaw, is left in the now shrinking wild west, forcing him to move south to avoid the law. His gang, led by a good friend, Dutch Van Der Linde, move down south in search of money and new opportunities. Morgan uses his quick-witted thinking along with his trigger finger &amp;amp; fists to lead their gang to a new beginning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>History Buffs Series - Hamilton Series - What Really Happened to Burr?</title>
      <link>https://the-yankee.github.io/news/post/2019/03/14/history-buffs-series-hamilton-series-what-really-happened-to-burr/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://the-yankee.github.io/news/post/2019/03/14/history-buffs-series-hamilton-series-what-really-happened-to-burr/</guid>
      <description>Preamble: In the Broadway Hip-Hop Musical, Hamilton, written by the incredibly talented star, Lin Manuel Miranda, Aaron Burr, the cold-blooded murderer of Alexander Hamilton, tells the story ofd the man he killed: founding father, Alexander Hamilton. Hamilton comes from Saint Croix to New York City, in search of refining his legacy and rising up to a new standard of living. The ambitious Alexander makes quick work, as he takes shots of ambition with his new group of friends: including John Laurens, Marquis de Lafayette, Hercules Mulligan, and his future killer, Aaron Burr.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>