<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Constitution on The Yankee</title>
    <link>https://the-yankee.github.io/news/categories/constitution/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Constitution on The Yankee</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://the-yankee.github.io/news/categories/constitution/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Free Speech - Why America NEEDS Hate Speech - First Amendment Legislation</title>
      <link>https://the-yankee.github.io/news/post/2019/07/23/free-speech-why-america-needs-hate-speech-first-amendment-legislation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://the-yankee.github.io/news/post/2019/07/23/free-speech-why-america-needs-hate-speech-first-amendment-legislation/</guid>
      <description>Within recent events, whether it be the bomb threats on Democratic Candidates, the Congressmen massacre, or the “Trump Whistle Blowing” events, society has blamed public speakers and their perceived message of “whistling for” or “inciting” violence for these horrific events of inhumanity.
Both Republicans and Democrats have been quick to blame the opposite side for “inciting” violence or “whistling” for it. In 2017, former presidential candidate, Bernie Sanders, at a rally for public assembly, he exclaimed how a healthcare bill which was just passed by Congress was going to “kill millions of people!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Immigration Migration - The U.S. Immigration Problem Solution - Federalist 46.</title>
      <link>https://the-yankee.github.io/news/post/2019/07/23/immigration-migration-the-u.s.-immigration-problem-solution-federalist-46./</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://the-yankee.github.io/news/post/2019/07/23/immigration-migration-the-u.s.-immigration-problem-solution-federalist-46./</guid>
      <description>The immigration problem in the United States has been publicized as one of the most divisive issues that divides the modern political biosphere. Both Republicans and Democrats have chosen their sides of this issue; conservatives, taking mostly isolationist and defensive standpoints on illegal immigration, and liberals, taking a more sympathetic standpoint on immigrants.
Southern Republican states are the main campaigners for border security and reform, while Western Democratic states endorse sanctuary states for pardoning illegal immigrants.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trump -- How Constitutional Are His Policies?</title>
      <link>https://the-yankee.github.io/news/post/2019/01/30/trump-how-constitutional-are-his-policies/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://the-yankee.github.io/news/post/2019/01/30/trump-how-constitutional-are-his-policies/</guid>
      <description>President Donald J. Trump is a divisive president, to say the least. He is often described as ‘unfit’ to be President of the United States. Whether this statement is true or not, are his policies constitutional?
His policies have inspired controversy upon both sides of the political spectrum, but should his executive orders hold up in the supreme court?
First, let’s look at the behemoth of the Trump Administration: ‘The Wall’.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>